<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jitesh Mulchandani</title>
    <link>https://jiteshvm.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jitesh Mulchandani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:59:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jiteshvm.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using git submodules</title>
      <link>https://jiteshvm.github.io/posts/using-git-submodules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiteshvm.github.io/posts/using-git-submodules/</guid>
      <description>Suppose you have a repository called mainrepo and another repository called subrepo that you want to use inside mainrepo. You can just clone subrepo inside mainrepo and use it. However, if subrepo gets updated frequently, then you will have to clone it everytime and replace it inside mainrepo. If you want to view the history of commits made to subrepo , then you need to go to the remote repository where you cloned it from and see it there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://jiteshvm.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiteshvm.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>EntwinedEntwined is a game about two souls, a bird and a fish, that are in love but can’t be together. Once united, the two souls will transform into a magnificent soaring dragon. Its available on PS4, PS3, Vita, iOS and Android. Ninja ChallengeIt uses head tracking as a gameplay mechanic. The player should move their head to the designed position to find the weak spot on the ninjas and punch them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jiteshvm.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiteshvm.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Jitesh. I am currently working as a programmer at Sony&amp;rsquo;s PixelOpus Studio in San Mateo. We released our first game called Entwined for PS4, PS3, PS Vita, iOS and Android. It is the first commercial game that I worked on and will always have a special place in my heart.
Before joining Sony, I got my Masters in Entertainment Technology from Carnegie Mellon&amp;rsquo;s Entertainment Technology Center (ETC). During this period, I did an internship at Microsoft where I worked with the Kinect Fun Labs team to create a bite-sized experience called Ninja Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jiteshvm.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jiteshvm.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>email : jiteshvm at gmail dot com 
linkedin : https://linkedin.com/in/jitesh-mulchandani-5b227437 
twitter : https://twitter.com/jiteshvm
github : https://github.com/jiteshvm
stackoverflow : https://stackoverflow.com/users/922347</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>